Aaqib Ahmad sheikh

Assistant Manager



Dedicated professional skillful in cash collection, data entry, Management and quality check. Resourceful and adaptable individual with extensive experience in handling Load of work to provide best customer experience. Comfortable in handling complex issues, meeting strict deadlines and adjusting to rapidly changing conditions. Reliable individual with skills and experience as Assistant Manager. Smart and committed to job well done and offering exceptional drive.

Contact

Address

Khull chohar Anantnag Kashmir, India 192201

Phone

6006240351

E-mail

nabiaaqib69@gmail.com

Skills

<u>Accounting</u>

Quality control

Management

Marketing

MS-word

Ms-Excel

Ms-Powerpoint

Ms-Excel

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Lightroom

Work History

2018-08 -2019-08

Captian Waiter

Grills Restaurant, Srinagar

- Handled customer Orders With ease.
- Guided newly joined waiters through the process of customer engagement.
- Optimized time between order and delivery.
- Prepared Tables (Reserved as well as un-reserved)

2019-08 -2020-8

Supervisor

Grills Restaurant, Srinagar

2020-08 -

Supervisor

2023-08 Golden Rice Indian Restaurant, Saudi Arabia

- Managed Staff Rotas Planning Effectively and Strategically.
- Managed Daily Planning of Workplace Operations, Cleary Communicating
- Build Customer Retention and Satisfaction By Delivering Top Quality Service.
 Increased Team productivity through Effective staff planning, coordination and task deligation.
- Maintained Spotless and Tidy Working Areas To Create Risk-free and Productive Environments.
- Managed Ledger-Book and Cash Collection.

Education

2019

2016 - Bachelor of Arts 2019 University of Kashmir - Jammu and Kashmir , India

2014 - 12th: Arts

2015 Government Boys Higher Secondary school - Mattan Anantnag, jammu and kashmir

Diploma in Information and Technology: IT

High School Diploma - : Science

Government Higher Secondary School - Anantnag Kashmir